## Mark Homa

Present Address 165 S Delaware Ave Apartment 2 Yardley, PA 19067 Contact Information markjhoma@gmail.com (215) 603-6280

# **Summary**

Mr. Homa is a dedicated professional with expertise in the sales, marketing, accounting, and finance. He has demonstrated abilities in business management, revenue generation, cost savings, and creative problem solving. He is a self-starter with strong interpersonal and communication skills.

### Education

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration - Finance Shippensburg University, Shippensburg PA

### Experience

Marketing Analyst, Insurance Expert Network LLC, Morrisville PA

2015-Present

- Provided marketing services that helped to expand the business portfolio
- Performed financial analysis that led to increased revenue generation

President and Owner, Advance Realty Preferred Properties LLC, Morrisville PA 2005-2015

- Helped clients reach family legacy goals
- Increased clients cash flow and overall net worth
- Improved clients business infrastructure and portfolio performance
- <u>Licenses:</u> Series 7, Series 66, Life and Health Insurance, Property & Casualty, Real Estate, Real Estate Agency

Account Executive, CBS Outdoor / Viacom / Outfront Media, Philadelphia PA 2004-2005

- Sold out-of-home advertising space to local, national, military, and sports accounts
- Developed new business with advertising agencies

### President and Owner, HOMA Inc., Morrisville PA

1992-2005

- Sold consumer products to businesses
- Maximized price-cost margins
- Established clients in new markets
- Maintained the business while caretaking parents

# Financial Analyst-Manager, CBS Corp., New York NY

1981-1992

- Progressively assumed more responsible management positions from entry level to Financial Manager
- Developed and implemented effective and efficient process systems
- Reduced costs and increased productivity
- Supervised professional and support personnel
- Forged close relationships with corporate affiliates, leading to radio voice overs
- Increased market share for clients in profitable markets